U.S. Economics Cooperation Administration Press Releases 5388
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Economics Cooperation Administration Press Releases
1949-1953
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States Economic Cooperation Administration
5388
2.5 cubic feet
2.5 linear ft.
Records (documents).
This collection consists of the releases of the Office of the U.S. Special Representative in Europe providing information about labor and labor conditions. The collection consists of two series, "For Your Information." and "Labor Information," subdivided by country and filed alphabetically for the years, 1950-1951.
5622235
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 18, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 11, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Reconstruction (1939-1951); United States. Economic Cooperation Administration
5622235
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, Austria, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  9/10/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, Belgium, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  8/18/1950
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, Denmark, 1949-1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, Europe (General), 1949-1951 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  11/18/1949 - 11/19/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, Finland, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  11/9/1950
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, France, 1949-1952 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  12/14/1949 - 1/10/1952
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, East Germany, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  4/19/1950 - 10/24/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, West Germany, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  11/19/1951; 2/21/1951; 7/31/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, Great Britain, 1949-1951 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  11/10/1949 - 9/13/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, Greece, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  12/13/1949
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, Hungary, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  9/11/1949
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1949-1951 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  11/28/1949 - 11/5/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, International Trade Secretariats, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  3/25/1950 - 7/12/1950
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, Ireland, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  6/9/1950
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, Italy, 1949-1951 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  12/17/1949 - 16/1/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, Netherlands, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  2/2/1950 - 8/31/1950
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, Norway, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  3/23/1950 - 2/6/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, Pakistan, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  8/1/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, Poland, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  6/19/1950 - 9/11/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, ECA/OSR Activities Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  12/22/1949 - 5/1-17/1950
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, Russia and Satellites, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  3/2/1950 - 5/22/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, Sweden, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  2/2/1950 - 5/1/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, Switzerland, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  5/3/1950 - 1/31/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, USA, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  1/5/1950 - 8/2/1950
- Project News Mutual Security Agency, 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Productivity and Technical Assistance Division; September 1 1951 - July 1952
- Economic Cooperation Administration, FYI Series, USA, 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  8/8/1950 - 10/3/1951
- Labor Information, 1952-1953 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  4/18/1952 - 1/2/1953
- Economic Cooperation Administration, L Series, Miscellaneous, 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Contains "Monthly Report of the Mutual Security Agency to the Public Advisory Board: Economic Development in Western Europe", May 31 1952
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, Austria, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  6/15/1950 - 7/30/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, Belgium, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  2/6/1950 - 3/30/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, Brazil, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  1/19/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, Czechoslovakia, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  9/6/1949
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, ECA/OSR Weekly Activities Report, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  9/2/1949 - 12/12/1949
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, Denmark, 1949-1951 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  9/21/1949 - 10/8/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, Estonia, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  6/3/1949
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, Europe and Asia (General), 1949-1951 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  7/19/1949 - 8/27/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, Finland, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  4/3/1951 - 6/4/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, France, 1950-1952 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  1/18/1950 - 9/19/1952
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, East Germany, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  6/24/1950
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, West Germany, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  3/24/1950 - 10/5/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, Great Britain, 1949-1951 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  8/9/1949 - 6/25/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, Greece, 1950-1951 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  1/5/1950 - 10/19/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, Iceland, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  5/10/1950
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  11/30/1949 - 6/20/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, International Labor Organization (ILO), 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  3/28/1950 - 5/25/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, International Trade Secretariats, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  4/20/1950 - 9/7/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, Italy, 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  11/28/1949 - 5/20/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, Korea, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  1/31/1950
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, New Zealand, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  9/20/1949
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Miscellaneous, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  6/1/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, Netherlands, 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  9/19/1949 - 8/23/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, North Africa, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  5/21/1950
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, Norway, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  1/27/1950 - 8/9/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, Philippine Islands, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  3/16/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, Poland, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  1/30/1950 - 2/13/1950
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, Russia and Satellites, 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  8/4/1949 - 4/11/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, Sweden, 1949-1951 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  7/7/1949 - 9/4/1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, Switzerland, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  3/11/1950 - 10/17/1950
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, Trieste, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  5/10/1950 - 9/1/1950
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, United States of America, 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  September 1950 October 1951
- Economic Cooperation Administration, Labor Information Series, World Federation of Trade Unions, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  5/21/1950- 9/14/1950
- Economic Cooperation Administration, European labor Division, Labor Who's Who, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  February 15, 1950
- ERP, Miscellaneous, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  In German; 19 - 20 January 1950
- ERP Trade Union Advisory Committee Labor News Bulletin, 1949-1952 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  September2 1949 - April 1952
- Office of the US High Commissioner Hicog for Germany, Miscellaneous, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  October 13 1950
- HICOG Statistical Reports (Employment and Unemployment, Germany), 1950-1952 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  September 26 1950 - January 22 1952